Guide to the Computer Services, Academic Computing, User Services records, 1967-1986.
Computer Services, Academic Computing, User Services records,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Computer Services, Academic Computing, User Services records, 1967-1986.
50-2-1935
Cornell University. Academic Computing, User Services.
10 cubic feet
Correspondence, printed material, and organizational files.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Memoranda, notes, correspondence, reports, publications, keypunch cards, and printouts document the development of academic computing, especially in the field of user services at Cornell University.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Office of Computer Services became Cornell Computer Services in 1979.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Memoranda, notes, correspondence, reports, publications, keypunch cards, and printouts document the development of academic computing, especially in the field of user services at Cornell University. Files of John D. Aiken relating to his activities as Computer Services Program Coordinator, 1972-1974, and Coordinator of Remote Computing, 1974-1976, include information about personnel, interactive computing, University planning, regional operations, hardware, and technical questions. Files of Joan M. Winters, Applications Programmer, 1970-1976, and Coordinator for User Support, 1976-1980, relate to her responsibilities as a consultant, applications programmer, lecturer, and technical writer and editor. There is information on applications software, systems facilities, and Office of Computer Services policies and procedures including HASP system testing, design of Production Control procedures, organization of seminar series, coordination of short courses on computing with the Department of Computer Science, development of installation and maintenance procedures for libraries of public applications software, as well as supervision of student and staff consultants, and development of mechanisms for communications among consultants.
Special projects documented include a student course appraisal project; software evaluation project; PBM/STIRS, a computer system for the identification of unknown mass spectra; and contract consulting for local implementation of SPINDEX II, software for producing printed registers and indexes of archival material.
Manuals from the 1980s for using MVS, SAS (Statistical Analysis System), a User's Guide to the Cornell MAIL System, Introducing IBM Computers at Cornell. Waterloo SCRIPT User's Guide.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Aiken, John D.; Winters, Joan M.; Aiken, John D.; Winters, Joan M.
Subjects:
Computers.; Computer literacy.; Computer software.; Computer software -- Testing.; Electronic data processing departments.; Computer literacy; Computer software; Computer software -- Testing; Computers; Electronic data processing departments
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Personnel files in Boxes 1 and 9 are restricted.
SERIES LIST
Series I. John Aikin Files
Series II. John Winters' Files
CONTAINER LIST
- John Aikin Files, 1968-1976
  - Office Files, 1968-1976
    - Regional Operations, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Correspondence, memoranda about remote users and general OCS information
    - Resumes and job applications, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Access Restrictions Apply
    - Personnel Information, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Resumes, correspondence, personal appraisals
    - Usage Protection, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Correspondence and survey on projected use of interactive computing for instruction
    - CU travel forms, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Area II Coordinating Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Correspondence on regional computing (John Rudan file)
    - Area II Coordinating Committee, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Survey of academic computing in the region
    - Grant Request, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Interactive computing as an instructional resource
    - History, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Interactive Computing at Cornell prior to 9/72, memos and reports
    - Introduction to Interactive Computing, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Draft and report by John Aiken
    - Computer Plans, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Reports about alternatives for increasing computer capacity
    - 168 Task Force, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Memos and notes about installation and regional prospects
    - FCR Report/Response, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Report of Faculty Council of Representatives, OCS memos and estimates
    - Computer Use Survey 1972-1973, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Responses to survey
    - Communications Vendors, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Information, correspondence and agreements about TYMSHARE and TYMNET
    - CMS/APL, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Correspondence about running APL in CMS
    - Telecommunications, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Status of requests list and design considerations for ASCII/EBCDIC conversion
    - Security, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Correspondence and report
    - Miscellaneous, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Articles and memos on various topics
  - User Service Files, 1972-1976
    - Terminal Operations, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      memos and student report on terminals in dorms
    - Uris Usage Data, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      reports and statistics
    - HS and SST Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      weekly reports
    - Installation, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      guide to procedures, reports on installations
    - User Services and Conversions, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      printout and information on user services
    - Documentation, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      memos about user services
    - Space, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      memos and floor plan
    - US_CIRCUIT_ANAL, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      printouts
    - TSO Problems, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      printouts, notes, and memos
    - Data Set Migration, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      reports and memos
    - Disk Conversion, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      notes and memos
    - Miscellaneous Meetings, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      notes, memos and minutes
    - SST's, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      correspondence about terminals
    - VM/370, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      reports
    - Mini vs. 168, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 34)
      memos and reports
    - Harris, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 35)
      correspondence, agreement about equipment
    - Unitech, Inc, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      information on equipment
    - Management, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 37)
      OCS management meeting reports, memos about User Services
  - Plato IV Files, 1972-1974
    - PLATO - 4, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 38)
      notes, bibliography, reports
    - PLATO IV Project, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 39)
      correspondence
    - PLATO IV Demonstration, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 40)
      mailing list, memos, proposal for University support, lists of workshop participants, budgets
    - PLATO Demo Replies - Yes, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - PLATO Demo Replies - ?, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - PLATO Demo Replies - No, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - PLATO IV - Evaluation Articles, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- John Winters' Files, 1967-1980
  - OCS Publications, 1970-1979
    - AN 1-150, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - AN 151-, 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - TN, 1971-1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - P and P, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - OCS Bulletin, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - OCS Bulletin, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - OCS Bulletin, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - OCS Newsletters, 1969-1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - OCS Statistical Newsletter, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - OCS Users Manual, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - OCS Staff Manual, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Manuals, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - HASP Manuals, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Minidesk Manager 1, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Minidesk Manager 2, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Minidesk Manager 3, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Manuals, 1970-1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Manuals, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - CAG Handbook, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - TYPESET Manual, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - TYPIST Manual, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Lists of Reference Materials, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Internal Communications, 1967-1980
    - Announcements, 1967-1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Memoranda 1, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Memoranda 2, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Memoranda 3, 1974-1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Memoranda 4, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Memos, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - OCS Memos, 1971-1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - OCS Internal Memoranda 1, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - OCS Internal Memoranda 2, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - OCS Internal Memoranda 3, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - OCS Memos and System Information, 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Technical Services Memos, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Electronic Mail 1-4, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 13-16)
    - OCS Internal Communications, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - OCS Internal Communications, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - OCS Internal Communications, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - OCS Internal Communications, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - OCS Internal Communications, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - OCS Internal Communications, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - OCS Internal Communications, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - OCS Internal Communications, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - OCS Facilities Defect Reports, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Available Space Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Batch Use, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Installation Summaries, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Uris Terminal Complaint Forms, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Systems meetings, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Operations meetings, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Management meetings, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - User Services Files, 1970-1980
    - Accounting, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Backup, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Card File Recovery Procedure, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - CLASP, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      reports, seminar notes
    - CLASP, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      "A Simulation of the CLASP/OS/360 Operating System"
    - CMS, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      memos, reports, printouts, notes
    - Computer Abuse, 1970-1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      newsletter reprints, memos, committee reports
    - Computer Literacy, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Computing at Cornell, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      memos and reports concerning proposed conversions from 360 to 370
    - Computing Expenditure Survey, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      forms for State schools
    - Contracts, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Conversion 3330 to 3350, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      notes, memos
    - CP/CMS R3, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - CUMC, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      notes, correspondence, reports for and about a proposed course at the Medical College
    - Equipment Orders, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      memos, invoice, notes
    - Free Public User Tests, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Hamilton College, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      correspondence, memos, reports, documentation about time-sharing arrangements
    - Hamilton College, 1974-1979 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      correspondence, memos, notes
    - Human Factors, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      memos about HELP command
    - IBM Presentation, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Information, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      drafts, instructions, reports on TSO, CMS, OS and other topics
    - In-House Utilities, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      procedure descriptions, memos, reports
    - Installation Procedures, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Installations, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      schedules, reports and summaries of installations
    - Library Searching, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      notes and reports about TELENET
    - Marketing, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Network - Cornell, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      draft report on upgrade of Cornell's Data Network
    - Office Equipment, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      notes and memos on office remodeling
    - OS/VIS - HASP, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      notes, memos, reports on batch processing
    - Pending, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      correspondence on questions
    - PLC Fixes, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      "Bug Report" and enhancement request form
    - Publications - Administrative, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      memos and notes
    - Requests for Information, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - SCMS, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      memos, notes, reports
    - Systems Information, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Systems Problems Affecting Users, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Telecommunications, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 37)
      network status report, memo about problems
    - TSO 1, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      memos and draft report
    - TSO 2, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      report on proposed accounting system for TSO, notes, drafts, memos
    - TSO Away, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      printouts and notes about TSO to CMS conversion
    - TSO Away, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 41)
      VSAM Users Guide, other information about sharing between CMS and OS batch
    - TYMNET/TELENET Users, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 42)
      notes, brochures, memos, documentation
    - User Services 1, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 43)
      memos, notes, printouts
    - User Services 2, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 44)
      notes, memos, and reports
    - User Services - D. Bessel, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 45)
      notes, memos, reprints, reports
    - User Support - General Documentation, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - User Support/Instructional Computing meetings, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Visitors, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Staff, 1968-1980
    - Student Consultants, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      applications, schedules, rosters
    - Student Consultants - Schedules, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      hourly time reports
    - Student Consulting, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Summer Consulting, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      applications
    - Problems, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Agenda, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      consultants' staff meeting
    - Management, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      memos, printouts, financial memos
    - Consultant's logs, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Clark and Upson Graffiti, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Clark and Upson Graffiti, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Memos to Student Consultants, 1973-1977 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Memos to Student Op/Consultants, 1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Student Opcons, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      time schedules, manuals, memos
    - User Complaints, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - CS RA's for User Services, 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Student Operator Consultants, 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      notes, memos, and printouts
    - Hal Perkins, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Avi Vardi, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - OCS Personnel, 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      applications and interviews
    - Staff Consulting Schedules, 1977-1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Staff Consulting, 1974-1980 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      announcements, logs, list of manuals, notes
    - 1979 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - 1978 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - 1977 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - 1976 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - 1975 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Langmuir Operators Consulting, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Programmer file, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Custom Programming, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Seminars and Short Courses, 1973-1979
    - Seminars and Short Courses, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      announcements and reports
    - OCS seminars, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Seminars, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      census, HASP, APL
    - Seminar - Policy Evaluation Using Computer Models, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Seminars and Colloquia, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Seminars, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Seminars, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Seminar Handouts, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Short Courses, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - CS 107 Introduction to CMS, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Computer Courses, 1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Instructional Computing, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Intro. Slide Show, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Video Tapes, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Library, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      bibliographies, lists, McBee cards for sources on computers
  - Special Projects, 1968-1977
    - CIUE Maas Student Appraisal forms, reports, punch cards, printouts, 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Opscan Conversion, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Marshall, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      printouts, forms, notes for biological sciences appraisal
    - Course Evaluation Accounting Forms, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Course Evaluation Accounting Forms, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Course Evaluation Accounting Forms, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Student Appraisal, 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Forms, correspondence, printouts
    - Student appraisal - Ag. Econ. Grad Students Association, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - CAG Stat Pgms, 1968-1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      documentation of statistics programs
    - Lib. Project, 1970-1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      forms, notes, TNs, and documentation for statistics packages
    - Library Project, 1971-1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - OCS Software Library Project, 1971-1974 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      completed forms
    - Library Software Projects, 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      notes, reports, memos, and printouts
    - Software Evaluation Project, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      index of available publications, printouts
    - Software Evaluation Project, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - APT, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      printouts, hexdump
    - CATCHR, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      printout of program
    - CORNAP, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      completed form, notes, documentation
    - CMSP, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      printout of tape dump
    - LABELS, 1968-1974 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      forms, printouts, and documentation
    - PERT/CPM, 1966-1974 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      printout, documentation
    - QUICK (Box 6, Folder 22)
      IBM QWIC Index, KWIC job deck, Quick Index compiler
    - SIMSCRIPT, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      printout and tape dump
    - TEXTBOOK, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - TSIS, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      printout and documentation
    - TYPESET, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      printout, tape dump
    - World Dynamics Model, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Reports, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Meetings, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - PBM/STIRS, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      literature, reports, notes, reprints
    - Pending, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      correspondence, account forms, notes
    - TYMNET, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      procedures, descriptions, printouts and notes
    - Consulting, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Memos, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Output Distribution, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Publicity, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Reprints, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Accounting, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - User Documentation, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - PBM/STIRS, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 40)
      notes, memos, and usage statistics
  - Freshman Engineering Survey, 1975-1977
    - Mary Ott Project, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      project description, memos, documentation, notes
    - US Geological Survey (Kalter), 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      letters, notes, and accounting forms
  - Spindex, 1973-1979
    - SPINDEX, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      early documentation
    - SPINDEX, 1973-1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      correspondence, reports, documentation, reports, notes
    - Account forms, 1974-1978 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Grant Proposals, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      correspondence about and proposal for a conference
    - SPINDEX Users Conference, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      correspondence, tentative agenda
    - SPINDEX Users Conference, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Projects, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      inquiries about other applications, printouts
    - Reports from Other Users, 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Other Reports and Reprints, 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - SPINDEX Testing, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      correspondence, memos, and printouts
    - New York Historical Resources Center, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      clippings, notes, reports, documentation
    - NHPRC, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      guide project documentation
  - Argonne National Laboratory, 1973-1979
    - Argonne National Laboratory, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      correspondence, reports, documentation about the central information agency for AEC-funded computer programs
    - Argonne National Laboratory information, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      newsletters and brochures
    - SPEAKEASY, 1974-1979 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      newsletters, correspondence, reports, and documentation for a graphics system
    - SPEAKEASY Conference Proceedings publications, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - NAG, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      newsletter and correspondence of Numerical Algorithms Group
    - FUNPACK, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - SHARE, 1973-1978
    - SHARE, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - SHARE Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      reports, memos, publications, minutes
    - SHARE Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      memos, reports, newsletters, correspondence
    - SHARE, 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - SHARE, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - SHARE, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - SHARE 50, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Software Information, 1969-1979
    - Computer Software Packages, 1973-1979 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      Information on CSMP, VS APL, ACSL, V1M4, IEBUPDTX, APT, ALGOLW
    - ISIS, 1971-1977 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      notes, manual, correspondence
    - ISIS, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 28)
      notes, reports, documentation
    - ISIS, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 29)
      notes and documentation
    - LISP/PLANNER, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 30)
      manuals
    - MARK IV, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 31)
      punch cards and printouts
    - OSIRIS, 1970-1976 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      manuals, information about Inter-University Consortium for Political Research
    - REDUCE, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 33)
      notes, letters, and manual
    - Penn State SCRIPT Report, 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      manual
    - SCRIPT-Waterloo Script, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      newsletters
    - SESAME, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      SESAME Primer
    - SPIRES, 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      workshop, draft users guide, printouts
    - SPIRES, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      correspondence and notes
    - WATFIV, 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 39)
      correspondence, exact from manual
    - ZAP, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 40)
      documentation
    - Statistical Packages, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      information on GENSTAT, SAS, IMSL, and SPSS
    - BMDP, 1973-1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      listings, program updates, newsletters
    - CURFIT, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      program
    - IMSL, 1975-1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      newsletters and other information
    - MPS MPSX, 1975-1979 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      correspondence, notes, manuals
    - MPSX Rice Project, 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      documentation from Rice University
    - MPSX-MIP, 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      notes, memos and correspondence about use of MPSX and MIP by Department of Agricultural Economics
    - MPS, Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Manuals, 1968-1977
    - IBM Manuals, 1973-1976 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Agricultural Economics Manuals, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 10)